Litzen Nicole Nisperos

Full Stack Developer

Personal Information

Email

litzennisperos@gmail.com

Mobile no.

+639950878540

Address

Blk 4 Lot 4, Phase 8, Villena Street Vista Verde Executive Village, Cainta, Rizal, Philippines 1900

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/litzennisperos

GitHub

github.com/nisperos19

Website

litzen-nisperos.netlify.app

Skills & Competencies

- Angular
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- React
- Ionic Framework
- JavaScript (ES6+)
- TypeScript
- HTML/CSS3/SASS
- UI/UX design
- Tailwind
- Primeflex
- MySQL/SQLite
- RESTful API development
- Version Control (Git)
- Performance Optimization
- Code Refactoring
- Responsive Web Design
- Team Collaboration
- Problem Solving
- Mentoring and Coaching

Skilled Full Stack Web and Mobile Developer with almost 5 years of experience in implementing innovative web and mobile applications. Collaborative team player with a passion for refactoring and improving code quality, resulting in reduction in bug-related delays and increase in overall code quality.

Work History

Senior Developer

02/2020 - Present

LGUSuite, Inc.

- Developed scalable and robust Web/Mobile applications from scratch using Angular, Ionic, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, SQLite and React Native.
- Optimizing the performance of Web application, reducing load time and bounce rate.
- Create and Implement secured RESTful API's using NodeJS and Express.
- Create databases schema and perform data aggregation for analytics using MongoDB.
- Collaborating with Developers to improve the quality and maintainability of an existing codebase.
- Collaborating with Business Analyst's for development requirements, timeline and product feasibility check.

Retention Specialist

02/2019 - 10/2019

ResultsCX

- Data Entry and Documentation: Accurately document all interactions and transactions with customers in the company's database or CRM system.
- Collaborate: Collaborate with other departments, such as Sales or Customer Service, to coordinate efforts in retaining customers and improving the overall customer experience.
- Continuous Improvement: Continuously seek opportunities for personal and professional development to enhance retention skills and knowledge.
- Stay Informed: Stay up-to-date with product knowledge, pricing, and promotional offers to effectively communicate with customers.

Education

BS in Information Technology

2013 - 2017

University of Santo Tomas